<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PlaySeal</title><link>https://www.playseal.com/</link><description>Recent content on PlaySeal</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.playseal.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Golf Party</title><link>https://www.playseal.com/portfolio/golf-party/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.playseal.com/portfolio/golf-party/</guid><description>Play mini golf games and party with your friends!</description></item><item><title>Cut Fingers</title><link>https://www.playseal.com/portfolio/cut-fingers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.playseal.com/portfolio/cut-fingers/</guid><description>To play this game Put and keep your finger in the circle. When the blade drops, release your finger as soon as possible to evade it. In 2 Fingers or 3 Fingers mode, you need to put 2 or 3 fingers to fill all circles, and the blade will drops one by one, which will be really big challenge for you.
CAUTION: Do NOT play this game on hard floor or high place, you may drop your iPhone/iPod to the ground!</description></item><item><title>A Hungry Mouse</title><link>https://www.playseal.com/portfolio/cut-fingers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.playseal.com/portfolio/cut-fingers/</guid><description>mmmmm….. The cakes are sooo~ delicious! The mouse is really hungry for cake, what about you?
Cakes are NOT a lie in this game! Stack them up and eat them all! OM NOM NOM NOM NOM! If you like Tom &amp;amp; Jerry, you&amp;rsquo;ll definitly like this game!
Controls Tap the screen to drop a cake.
Tap the left/right half of the screen to control the mouse while eating cakes</description></item><item><title>Epic Games launches Unreal Engine 5</title><link>https://www.playseal.com/blog/epic-games-launches-unreal-engine-5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.playseal.com/blog/epic-games-launches-unreal-engine-5/</guid><description>Unreal Engine 5 is now available to download, Epic Games announced on Tuesday. The latest edition of the benchmark games development engine touts a new “fully dynamic global illumination” tool, plus a geometry system that allows creators to build games with “massive amounts of geometric detail.”
Epic announced Unreal Engine 5’s launch with a Twitch and Youtube livestream showing high-performance visuals and real-time rendering. Unreal Engine 5 will also use a new World Partition system that, Epic says, “changes how levels are managed and streamed,” by dividing up the game world into a grid and streaming only its necessary cells.</description></item><item><title>Dungeon Crawler Jam 2022</title><link>https://www.playseal.com/blog/dungeon-crawler-jam-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.playseal.com/blog/dungeon-crawler-jam-2022/</guid><description>In this context a dungeon crawler is a grid based RPG viewed in first person and with 90 degree turning. Examples of classic dungeon crawlers are Dungeon Master, Eye of the Beholder, Lands of Lore and Bard&amp;rsquo;s Tale etc.
For more examples check out the submissions in last year&amp;rsquo;s jam.
Game specific rules:
The game must have first-person exploration at all times. (See the above GIF). Exceptions are point to point overworld map movement (fast travel), combat screens, cut scenes, town screen, inventory screen other relevant screens.</description></item></channel></rss>